## Marlon Maniti

Front-End Developer / UI/UX Designer

address mobile email web Remuera, Auckland 1050 +64 22 354 3442 lonmaniti@gmail.com nolrm.github.io

summary

Front-End Developer who focuses on writing clean, elegant and efficient code. I craft websites with love.

**UI/UX Designer** with a passion for designing beautiful and functional user experiences. Minimalist who believes that less is more.

technical expertise

#### **Professional Skillset**

- W3C Validated HTML5
- CSS3 via SASS & Compass, Less, SCSS
- Twitter Bootstrap
- jQuery, JavaScript
- Website optimization + cross browser capabilities
- Responsive Design

#### **Working Knowledge**

- AngularJS, AJAX, JSON
- Jekyll, Grunt
- CMS (WordPress, Joomla)
- Velocity Templating (Server-side)

#### **Tools**

- SublimeText2
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Github
- Invision

employment

# **TORO.IO** Front-End Developer / Web Designer Philippines (May 2014 - July 2015)

Software development company that focused on producing on his own CMS with web application development tool.

- Created default widgets using Velocity Template(server-side templating) from the e-commerce API
- Scaffold the project to setup the needed build tools for the project (using npm and bower)
- Created UI-Kit Styleguide to be use for the TORO apps
- Design website, logo, icons and etc.
- Collaborated with Front-end and Back-end Developers for TORO tools improvement.
- Guides and act as a mentor to Front-end OJTs. Check and Review the OJTs codes, if they follow the basic coding standards for front-end development.

#### employment

#### **Huchcode** Junior Web Designer (June 2012 - May 2014)

Game development company partnered with Game on (Korea-Japan).

- Converts PSD to HTML5/CSS3(Smartphone and Feature Phone)
- Develop clean, valid(W3C), Responsive and Cross-Browser Compatibility
- Converted Flash to Google Swiffy/Create JS
- Created simple HTML5/JS using Adobe Edge
- Backend Templating (PHP)
- Design website, logo and other marketing materials.

#### Freelance (Feb 2012 - Present)

- Created responsive website and sometimes using CMS
- Designed website and logo

#### Advantpoint Inc. Web Designer (Sept 2011 - Feb 2012)

- Created website using Vivvo CMS and maintained company website
- Designed website and other marketing materials
- Troubleshooting PCs / Assist technical support

#### Metaverse Services Ltd. Online Game Support (Sept 2010 - Sept 2011)

Designed banner, logos and other marketing materials. Advertised company on different advertising websites.

### Mass Communication Studio On-the-job Trainee (Nov 2009 - Mar 2010)

Serves as Graphic Artist(Layout Brochure and other Marketing Materials). Design Title Cards for Maski Nanu TV Show. Answer phone calls and perform other administrative function, as it may be necessary.

education

**Holy Angel University,** Angeles City, Philippines Received a **Bachelor of Science** in Information Technology Major in Multimedia during April 2010.

References and code samples available upon request.

nolrm.github.io
lonmaniti@gmail.com